wideo.co 2019-08-03

# Wideo Privacy Policy

#### **1\. INTRODUCTION**

Wideo, Inc (hereinafter referred to as “Wideo”) respects your privacy and your personal information.

These privacy policies (hereinafter referred to as “Privacy Policies”) explain how Wideo uses, protects and shares the information provided by You (hereinafter referred to as “User’s information”) when using the website www.wideo.co (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”) or the services provided therein (hereinafter referred to as the “Services”), and the information collected about You. In addition, these Privacy Policies describe your alternatives regarding the uses of your information made by Wideo and how to access such data and update it.

These Privacy Policies must be read in conjunction with Wideo’s Terms and Conditions (hereinafter referred to as “Terms and Conditions”) currently included on the Site. Please read these Privacy Policies and the Terms and Conditions carefully before using the Site and its Services.

####  **2\. ACCEPTANCE**

Your access to the Site and the use of Services are subject to your acceptance of these Privacy Policies, and your acceptance and compliance with the Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree, you shall not access the Site or use its Services.

####  **3\. UPDATES**

Wideo reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change or modify these Privacy Policies, or delete parts of them at any time. If we apply changes, we shall notify you whichever way we consider most appropriate. If you do not wish to continue using the Services in accordance with the new changes, you may cancel and stop using our Services.

####  **4\. INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We may collect and store the following information:

 **4.1. Personal information provided by You:** Your Personal information (hereinafter referred to as “Personal information”) includes information relative to the identity You provide at the time of registration on Wideo.co. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name(s), e-mail address, mailing address, account names for social media to which you may link your Account, your picture or photographs, a personal description. You may decide not to provide your Personal information; however, in that case, some website features will not be available to You.

If you use the Service with any third-party application (Facebook or Google+) credentials, you authorize us to gather your authentication information, such as user name and encrypted access credentials.

 **4.2. Information we gather from You:** Every time You use the Service, or visit our website, we may use different technologies to collect relevant information. We may automatically collect the following information **:**

Technical data, which may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, URL information, data about cookies from the specific website you requested, your login information, browser type and version, server address, domain name, time zone settings, language, operating system, and platform.

Wideo may use such data to carry out traffic or business analysis, as well as to determine which Service and/or Site aspects are of greater or lesser utility to You.

 **4.3. Information about You collected from other sources**. We may also receive information about You from partners, service providers, payment services, advertising networks, search information providers.

####  **5\. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**

Wideo may use Cookies and similar technologies like pixels and mobile device identifiers to track your activity on the Site. Cookies are data files which are stored in your computer after you access certain websites. The information provided by cookies helps Wideo understand your preferences and improve your experience on the Site.

 **5.1. Essential or Operation Cookies:** These cookies are used by Wideo to provide You with the Site Service. For example, cookies which enable User identification and Site login.

 **5.2 Analytics Cookies:** These cookies allow us to analyze the Site access, use and performance in order to give You a better service.

 **5.3 Advertising Cookies:** These cookies are used to show adverts of products and/or services that may be of interest to You.

####  **6\. USE OF USER INFORMATION**

 **6.1.** Wideo uses your information to offer Site Services. This may include the following:

  1.  **** Provide, manage, customize, and improve our Service, third-party products and services, and advertising available through the Site or externally (on other sites you may visit).
  2.  ****Contact You for business and promotional purposes, or for reasons related to Service matters, by sending e-mails, notifications or other messages.
  3.  **** Help Wideo’s professional associates (hereinafter referred to as “Professional Associates”) in the process of Site design and operation, or the analysis of the User’s information gathered. Professional Associates will use the User’s information for the sole purpose of carrying out the work as agreed with Wideo, and shall be bound to keep its confidentiality.

 **6.2.** Apart from the exceptions provided for in this Privacy Policy, Wideo shall notify You or require your consent before your information is shared with any third party.

####  **7\. USER INFORMATION PROTECTION**

 **7.1.** In order to protect the User’s information, Wideo implements several security measures. For example, when introducing users’ sensitive information, Wideo encrypts such information through the use of the technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Additionally, Wideo follows generally accepted industry standards to protect your Personal information both when transmitted and received.

 **7.2.** In spite of the security measures implemented, Wideo may not ensure the security of the information disclosed by You. When using the Site and/or Services, you recognize and expressly accept that Wideo does not ensure the security of the data provided or received.

####  **8\. SHARED USE OF USER’S INFORMATION**

 **8.1. Information that You share:** If you link your Wideo’s account to any third-party application, you will directly share your activity. You understand and accept that such information may be attributed to your account in the third-party application, and may be disclosed in that service.

Wideo also allows you to share any specific content created by You using any third-party application, other third-party services, and other people. Please bear in mind that, if you post content in any third-party application or service, other people may see it.

 **8.2. Advertising Services** : Wideo may share information with advertising partners in order to send information about news of the services offered by the Site, or to show adverts of products or services that may be of interest to You.

 **8.3 Service providers:** Wideo may share your information with service providers required to provide our Service (e.g. marketing e-mail providers). If a third party processes user data on our behalf, it shall be subject to the security and confidentiality liabilities pursuant to this Privacy Policy and the current legislation. If a third party processes user data on your behalf, such processing is subject to its own Privacy Policy.

 **8.4. Protection for Wideo and others** : Wideo may disclose User’s information when it believes in good faith that it is necessary to comply with the law, enforce or apply the Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or to protect Wideo’s rights, property or security, as well as its employees’, customers’ and other people’s rights, property or security.

Wideo may also disclose your User’s information after receiving a court order or summons, or to collaborate with an investigation in compliance with the law, which may include the response to such summons or court orders.

 **8.5. Wideo’s Companies:** We may share information with Wideo’s family of companies. Such information is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

####  **9\. WITHHOLDING USER’S INFORMATION**

Wideo will only keep your User’s information to the extent (a) required by law; or (b) that it may be necessary to address any problem or question You may have. When the User’s information is no longer required, Wideo shall destroy or delete it.

####  **10\. LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES**

In order to enhance your use of the Site and the Services, Wideo may insert links to other third-party websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such sites. These links direct You out of the Site and are beyond Wideo’s control, and they may have their own privacy policies. Wideo is not responsible for such third-party sites’ content and activities. You may access to said websites at your own risk and responsibility.

####  **11\. PAYMENT**

Your credit card information will also be subject to the privacy policy of the payment processor used by Wideo. Please read the privacy policy included in the relevant payment processor’s website in order to get information about the use, storage and protection of your data before submitting any credit card information.

####  **12\. COMPANY TRANSFERS**

Wideo may transfer its business. In such case, the User’s information could be one of the company’s assets which may be transferred or acquired by the acquirer. You recognize and accept that such transfer may occur and any Wideo’s acquirer may continue using your User’s information in accordance with these Privacy Policies.

####  **13\. MINIMUM REQUIRED AGE**

Wideo shall never voluntarily request or accept personally identifiable information from Users under sixteen (16) years old. When using the Services, You warrant that you are sixteen (16) years old or older, or, as the case may be, that your parents or legal guardian have read and accept these Privacy Policies.

####  **14\. UNSUBSCRIPTION AND PERSONAL INFORMATION MODIFICATION**

 **14.1.** You may see and modify a great part of the information we obtain from You through your account and profile. If you wish to cancel your account, please visit app.wideo.co/login/, tap Profile settings and then Delete account. You may also choose not to receive any e-mail from Wideo at any time by clicking the option Unsubscribe that appears there. It is worth mentioning that, even though You may choose not to receive any e-mails from Wideo, Wideo reserves the right to contact You by e-mail regarding the specific products and services you may have requested.

 **14.2**. Wideo encourages You to update your Personal information when applicable.

####  **15\. REQUESTS AND/OR QUESTIONS**

If you have any request or question about these Privacy Policies or the information we have about You, you may contact us at info@wideo.co or by mail at **Wideo Inc.** **2140 20th st San Francisco, California (94107).**

We will respond to your request within a reasonable period of time after verifying your identity. We may reject those requests which are not proportional or required by law.
